☑ruijialin@gmail.com ८ 7184960737 in ruijialin 🗘 rayjialin

ABOUT

An iOS developer with a background in SAP consulting. I am experienced in creating iOS apps with users in mind, I also understand the importance of creating readable and maintainable source code. And I enjoy reading newsfeeds in the morning to learn about latest iOS news and updates.

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

Swift, Objective-C, C, Ruby, Javascript, HTML, CSS, ABAP

FRAMEWORKS & TESTING TOOLS

Core Animation, Foundation, Core Location, MapKit, AVKit, Parse, Realm, Firebase, Core Data, Cloud Anchor,

XCTest, UIKit, Core Graphics, ARKit

OTHERS

MVC, MVVM, SharePoint, Trello, PostMan, Outlook, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, SAP ECC6.0, SAP HANA, FS-CD

PROJECTS

July 2018 to Current

MultiPeer Selfie

A selfie taking app that connects multiple iPhones together to act as camera or remote to take selfie using multipeer connectivity

framework

May 2018 to Current

Beer Pong AR

Tech Stack: (Firebase, Cloud Anchor, ARKit, SceneKit, Core Animation)

• A multiplayer AR Beer Pong game that uses ARKit and Scenekit to create beer pong scene, and synchronize game state in

realtime using Firebase and Google Cloud Anchor

• We aimed to make playing beer pong game accessible to anyone and anywhere

May 2018 to Current

HeadsUP

Tech Stack: (Firebase, Core Location, GeoFire, MapKit, User Default)

• The app uses MapKit and Core Location to display user location on the map, GeoFire to detect nearby user within certain radius; and Firebase manages all the connections for each user

• The purpose of this app is to promote people to meet new friends and talk to people instead of looking down on their phones

EDUCATION

2018

Lighthouse Labs

Immersive iOS Developer Bootcamp 2018

2013

Barnard Baruch College

Computer Information Systems

EXPERIENCE

March 2017 to Sept. 2017

Sompo · SAP Business Analyst · Purchase, NY

Involved in FS-RI and FS-CD implementation from requirement gathering to go live phase

June 2013 to Feb. 2017

Virtusa · SAP Consultant · New York, NY

Client: ADP (06/2016 - 01/2017)

SAP Technical Consultant

- Worked on Electronic Federal Tax Payment System implementation to help clients to file taxes for their employees
- Configured SAP Gateway to connect with the front end system

Client: CareSource (04/2015 - 05/2016)

SAP Technical Consultant

· Worked on FS-CD implementation to automate their incoming payment process and payment clarification process

Client: United Guarantee (09/2013 - 03/2015)

SAP Techno-Functional Consultant

- · Created and performed technical unit testings, user acceptance testings and user security testing for various processes
- · Conducted requirement workshops with business users and project team for billing, payment and disbursement processes